Yo, Travon, what's up with PulseChain,
man? You ain't talking about PulseChain
no more. What about HEX? Okay, man,
let's talk about PulseChain. Let's get
into it. What's going on with
PulseChain? Whoa, it's been 3 years,
guys. Whoa.
Since PulseChain launched. I remember we
were waiting like 2 years for it to
launch. And it's been 3 years since it
launched. That's insane. So, as you can
see, we're pushing towards a new low
here. And before I get into that, I want
to remind you guys, there's a protocol
coming to more tokens.com called Fuel.
It's going to buy and burn more token,
which already has a very low liquidity.
You know, I'm not going to say that this
is going to pump, you know, a lot of ETH
into more, but it will finally have a
sustainable buy pressure. Um, as you can
see, we've already got a couple of
bigger buys coming in. This is also tied
to more on PulseChain via LP bonding.
So, you can see here, the prices of both
of these being at the the same contract,
we were able to tie them together, and
there's a arbitrage opportunity going on
between the two. So, excited to see how
Fuel plays out. Submit-to-Earn protocol.
Also, had another announcement just now
revealing the reward function and how
you're incentivized to either promote
the protocol or even just continue to
pump your own mints via continuing to
mine. Because your reward is a function
of everyone who mints after you, or
every address that mints after you. So,
be on the lookout for this. Come join
the Telegram. A lot of excitement in the
Telegram, a lot more excitement than
usual. We've even got Barter Town uh
throwing shout-outs in his Telegram
about it. He is excited about it. White
paper is coming soon. Testnet is coming
soon. Uh, shooting for the end of this
month for the launch. So, it's about 2
weeks from now.
All right, let's get back to PulseChain.
So, PulseChain looks like it's about to
make a new low. So, what am I What What
are my thoughts on the overall
situation? So, we have a guy. He builds
a reputation for about 2 years using
Bitcoin. Then uses that leverage to
promote his own project called Hex. He
launches Hex. It goes 24,000%
You know, and looking back on it, you
know, in hindsight, it's like, "Oh,
yeah." It's kind of funny because the
the way liquidity and all that I mean,
he actually was ahead of his time
because he understood liquidity way
before, you know, any of us could really
see what was really happening. But, the
the fact of the matter is the liquidity
was just really, really low, and he had
all the supply. So, it was easy to pump,
and once it got momentum, the community
was just so strong just shilling it. It
was really Looking back, that was an
impressive scam. I mean, it wasn't a
scam, but cuz I mean, you could have
won. But, so did BitConnect, you know,
BitConnect pumped a lot, too. So, it's
like, "Eh." I think it's safe to say it
I don't want to I still don't I still
don't want to call Hex a scam because
it's still running. I'm actually
continuing to stake. Uh we'll talk about
that. Let's talk about it now. So, you
guys know what happened with PulseChain.
I don't I don't need to go in and give
you the full history. But, for those of
you that are new, let's let's do it. So,
he launches Hex. Hex pumps a lot, and he
announces PulseChain, which fuels it
even more. And then, we're A lot of the
community was thinking that PulseChain
was going to be in the next couple of
months. You can kind of see that here.
And then, we just have the delay, delay,
delay. And I think maybe around here
PulseChain la- I don't remember where
PulseChain launched at.
Um I think it said May 23rd. So, back
here is when PulseChain launched. And
then, it A lot of shenanigans, you know,
he's dressing funny. I mean, that's back
here. But, he's really, you know, doing
a lot of things to hurt Hex, saying how
EthHex is the wrong Hex, not the real
Hex, something that's like right here.
Just a lot of negativity surrounding him
and Hex. Um fast forward to now, Richard
Heart is still tweeting. Now, I'm
blocked, so I can't uh really look into
deep to his tweets, but he's doing a lot
of the same things he was always doing,
you know, shaming and, you know, really
into the legal stuff. Um government type
stuff, government talk, but he's not
talking about PulseChain or Hex or any
of that. So, this guy's sitting here
talking about HVAC tech.
You know, air conditioner pumps heat
into your house outside. They only draw
power for two fans and a comp- a
compressor. Not having one hurts you and
helps no one. Sincerely, an HVAC tech.
So, I guess so apparently he's an HVAC
tech now, you know, so best net- best
network was down a couple hours today.
That was back in June. Fun idea, US
government. A lot of the same, you know,
stuff that is important, but nobody I
mean, he's got a lot of engagement, but
I think people are just engaging because
they were like they want to just
PulseChain, man. Like I don't I don't I
think if it weren't for him growing that
community of die hard Hexicans,
Pulsicans, I don't think he would be
getting this much engagement. Cuz I
don't know this is stuff that I mean, I
don't care about it, but maybe maybe
someone does. Talking about gold,
Bitcoin, Ethereum, you know, talking
about only Ethereum, just not talking
about his projects. So, it looks like
he's given up on it. Now, the rational
part of me says, yeah, he's given up on
it. He's trying to let just let it let
it fade into the the abyss, let people
forget about it, don't talk about it,
and I really want to see if in his
comments, Liberty Swap is at number one.
Keith Executive, my brother in Christ,
we we know things are down bad. I'm not
sure what the angle is, but if Peter
Schiff replied with the hex chart. Okay.
Now, this is interesting. He didn't
block this guy. You know, this is very
interesting that he didn't block this
guy. Now, you notice how the naive This
is the naive side of my brain starting
to kick in trying to be like, "See, he's
letting people talk trash now." You
know, so I was going to say just I
imagine that I would come here and
anybody talking about hex or PulseChain
was getting blocked. Okay, now do
PulseChain, you know. [clears throat]
So, he's letting He's not really
blocking anymore, which is interesting,
but the naive side of my brain still
thinks that this could get ran back.
This whole thing hex PulseChain, will
it? I don't know.
But, it could very easily be ran back.
And what I mean by that is you have
Richard Heart here. You know, he sold a
lot. And if he didn't, he provide
liquidity and remove like he did
something like legally. Maybe he
provided liquidity and exited that way.
You know, probably, you know, cuz that's
not selling. So, he has a lot of funds,
I'm sure. Now, hex on ETH, which is the
hex that I'm
really I lean more towards the hex on
ETH because I know ETH is going to be
around. PulseChain is looking obsolete.
We'll get into that. But, the market cap
of hex right now is 23 million. It's
funny, hex has 9 million holders. Now,
somebody airdrop I guess 9 million hex
to every wallet that had something on
Ethereum, which is pretty cool. So, the
community still does still try to
promote hex, but it just ends up just
not being enough. So, the PulseChain
bridge has 19%. So, what we know is this
is showing all liquid hex. This is not
counting the staked hex. Now, do I want
to go in and see how much staked hex? It
doesn't really matter because he owns
the full supply. So, to count the stake
tax, it's not going to be much because
it's only going to be 600 billion HEX is
staked and there is 52 billion liquid.
Now, the problem is we don't know the
percent I don't I mean, we probably do,
but I don't remember how much he owns of
this. It's probably
92% of it's locked. So, it's probably he
probably it's like 500 million maybe 500
million or something like that. He he's
got to himself. So, it doesn't really
matter. The market cap is around it's
actually much much larger than this, but
you can't really count it because he's
not going to be dumped he if it starts
to pump, this is the only number that's
going to matter. Put it like that. So,
it's not like you have to worry about
the sell pressure of his wallets. In the
In it's staked anyway. So, which is
actually kind of pretty bullish. So,
what do I truly think? Here's what I
truly think and I'm going to use a coin
that I bet a lot of you guys will
remember. It's called WISE. Now,
interesting thing happened with WISE
lately. Now, if you don't know WISE,
WISE is basically a revenge fork from
someone in the HEX community who
launched WISE, which actually WISE has
the largest liquidity on Ethereum right
now. I think it's on V2, but it has the
largest liquidity 52 million. The entire
It's actually better than HEX. Like,
I'mma keep it real with y'all. I've been
buying and staking WISE max term because
of it's the the whole setup. Like, look
at Just Just look at the numbers. If you
look at these numbers then you can be
like, "Oh, yeah, that's probably
pretty." Now, it does just go down and
down and down versus ETH, but that's why
I'm about to show you this. So, a couple
of months ago, WISE completed its first
full stake cycle cuz the max stake
length on WISE is 5 years and as you can
see, it's been 5 years and 6 months.
So, right before that or right after,
there was this huge candle that came in.
Now, keep in mind, this is a 51 million
or 100 million liquidity pool, but $51
million liquidity pool. So,
this is kind of kind of like expert
level stuff here. But, to make this kind
of candle, you need a lot of money. So,
someone with a lot of money said, "Oh,
the shares are expiring. I can come in
and buy those expired shares." And
that's what happened. So, here's what I
truly think's going to happen with HEX.
I actually think, which is hilarious in
hindsight, but I actually think it is a
15-year cycle thing that is going to be
another We're almost We're coming up on
halfway, almost 2,500 days. I honestly
think, and this is why I still buy and
stake HEX, but in small amounts every
now and then, you know, I don't go
crazy, but every now and then I'm in the
mood, I'm like, you know, I'm feeling
like, "Mhm, I'm feeling long-term. Let
me throw a HEX stake." because
it's down a lot.
You know, so you can get a lot. You can
get like 100,000 HEX for a couple bucks
now, or something like that. I don't
know. But, and that was a lot back then,
so, you know, and I'm doing the max
term. So, what I actually think is going
to happen is I think we're going to get
[snorts] one of these candles
around day 555. We're going to get one
of these candles like this, and I think
it'll possibly keep going, you know,
because it'll probably be orchestrated.
But, I think it's going to be a lot like
Big Pay Day. There's going to be a lot
of
uh shares expiring, and let me explain
what happened with WISE. Now, you can
see it on Well, I don't know if you can
see it on this, because I don't have the
I don't have my wallet connected here.
But, essentially, what happened on WISE
after this big boost right here, the APY
went up because of those shares expired.
And, and you know, everyone didn't
unstake, everyone didn't restake.
There's going to be a lot, you know, a
lot of change happened on this right on
this right here. So, APY went up because
there's less there was instantly less
competition cuz the shares expired. So,
I'm thinking the same thing will happen.
So, that's one thing about Hex. Do I
think it's going to he's going to come
back and pump it one day? I do actually
think that. I do, yeah, yeah. I do. I
think he's just waiting and he's and
then he kind of just you look back, he's
really been trying to push it down. Like
he's really trying to not like he's like
forcing himself now maybe not force
himself or really going out of his way
to not talk about PulseChain and Hex.
And that's because and I know that it's
not like I I not it's not that I know
that, but low-key I do the same thing
with more. Like it's like the lower I
can keep the price of more, the easier
it is for it to go up when I get excited
about it again. So, the lower he gets
Hex to go, the easier it'll be when he
finally wants to pump it and he won't
have to do use much of his resources,
which is funds and his time. So, am I
still in that in the cult of Hex?
A little bit. I kind of believe that
he's going to come back and do
something. I think he's just waiting for
this to get really little because the
lower this goes, the easier you can get
it to run. Now, PulseChain. PulseChain
is different and I
what I actually think Wow, look at that.
More is the biggest gainer on
PulseChain. That's pretty cool. Here's
the PulseChain chart. So, PulseChain
just made a new low. Um
45 million market cap. Let's look at the
explorer, which I don't know if it even
works. That's been a meme for a while
now. PulseChain doesn't have a working
explorer. 8% is held here. Kind of want
to say that must be Richard Heart's.
Yes, got to be. Thousand days ago,
definitely his wallet. I don't know. Is
that the I don't know, guys. I I I'm not
even going to lie to you guys. I don't
know.
Lot of stuff I don't know cuz I'm not
really looking into this stuff lately.
But let's look into it. Let's look at
some of the stats. So, price history,
know how that We know how that's going
on how that's going. Total active
wallets has still getting new active
wallets. Daily active users is down. Not
a ton. It's really about the same as
always been. Daily transactions is
actually trending up. Like, we can see
little the lows here are kind of going
up here. So, that's interesting.
Not sure what all the transactions are,
but pulse burned 13 million pulse burned
today. That doesn't sound like a lot.
Yeah, pulse chain is a different beast
because duh, we don't really need pulse
chain now, man. ETH gas fees are down.
You can end your hex stakes and they're
It's kind of expensive transaction, but
it's It doesn't make a dent in I mean,
unless it's you stake really, really
small amounts, which is like, okay. But
now, I'm just more into hex. Like, I'm
always thinking about how much hex I
could get. When I I don't Am I buying
pulse chain? Not really. I already have
my I mean, maybe It's kind of like you
should get some because it's down so
much. You can probably like if you're
still holding it, you know, you can
probably buy some and increase your
holdings a lot um to take away from the
loss. But I mean, it's down a lot. Like,
you it pretty much went to zero. Like,
could it come back? Yeah, he's still
alive. So, there's that.
>> [laughter]
>> Then, can the community bring it back?
The community's going to have to learn
something really dope. I don't think so.
Think we've got our blockchains. If
you're not Robinhood or somebody
massive, it's going to be pretty hard to
get people to come over and do something
on your chain. And that's why for more,
with this fuel build, I'm going to just
rock with Ethereum. Now, they people are
asking me am I going to put this on
pulse chain? I tried I actually tried to
put fuel on pulse chain, but I think
that from what I remember, there's
something about the priority fees or the
base fees or something with pulse chain
where this fuel protocol would not work.
But again, remember I I said that
they're LP bonded, so wherever the one
on more goes or wherever the one on
pulsechain goes, they're going to go
together. Now, this being tied to
pulsechain, I don't think it hurts it
too much because I mean, pulsechain is
not going to go down much more. I mean,
if it's going to go down, I mean, it
could keep going down to to zero, but if
you look at the market cap of
pulsechain, it's already 43 million. So,
it it's hex and pulsechain shouldn't be
going down too much more. They they
can't continue to slide. They could
slide another 50% sure, but the big
losses have already been set in. So, I
don't think it's really that big of a
problem for more to be paired to pulse
to pulse. There's really actually more
upside on There's actually more upside
potential on pulse than there is on
Ethereum. So, if anything, the Ethereum
would might would hold it down. But, um
what am I doing on pulsechain? The only
pulse only pulsechain project outside of
more that I'm really rocking with is
this vouch protocol. Now, I have all of
my pulse in VPLS,
their VPLS token, which is staked pulse.
Now, this should be going up versus
pulse. Yes. So, this goes up versus
pulse indefinitely. So, I already have a
a pulsechain earner, so to speak. And
then they have their vouch token that
uses validator fees to buy back and burn
the token. Now, it's going down a lot,
too. Pretty sure that's mostly because
pulsechain has been going down. So, look
at it versus pulse. So, yeah, it's kind
of trending up a little bit versus pulse
over time. But, you know, these are like
hedges of versus pulse. It's pulse is
infla- I mean, it's deflationary because
it's got its burn, which is you know,
it's it's been deflating. So, that's
good. Yeah, I think it's a it's a it's a
lot, man. I think it's Here's my last
verdict. First off, come to the Telegram
for more. Go to the website. We're
actually going to push an update to
moretokens.com today for more staking.
So, that's going to be a There's going
to be an update there for you to stake
your more on PulseChain. So, your more
on PulseChain, you can come stake some
more. A lot better. It's going to look
the same, but it's going to be some new
stats and stuff to look at. Um
but, come to the Telegram, go check out
the tweets, be on the lookout for the
white paper for fuel. And my last
verdict is pivot to something. I mean,
it's too late
to It's too late to sell, for sure, now.
Like, if you've been holding out I would
not recommend selling and be like,
"Okay, man, I'm selling, getting out of
this." No, just uh
I'm I would recommend I mean, this isn't
financial advice, but I'm going to I
mean,
is it financial advice at this time
you're not down 99% and I'm telling you
to keep holding? Like, I don't think so.
But, I actually just think that he's The
last thing is PulseChain, HEX, all that
is like sub 10 million market cap. If
those things are sub 10 million market
cap and he's still I mean, I would
almost say I would say the point I give
up and be like, "Okay, he's not ever
pumping this." is HEX is under a million
market cap. Or say it's like a million
market cap, which isn't that far. I
mean, it's down a good bit, but I don't
think it could actually could get that
cheap. But, I mean, if it gets that
cheap, then you might want to stake some
because it's so cheap. So, it's kind of
it's it's it's it's tricky. Um yeah, I
think that it's possible. I wouldn't
count on it, though. I'm not counting on
it. So, I'm not sitting around buying
HEX every day, staking it, buying
PulseChain, waiting for Richard Heart.
Probably not going to happen, but I
definitely could see it coming. He's got
to stay alive, though. He's getting kind
of old. Like, he's probably got all gray
now.
He's probably pushing what? He's
probably like in his 50s by now, right?
So, you don't want to depend on anyone
like that. That's my verdict. Every now
and then, I buy some HEX to keep my
15-year ladder going because I think I
mean even if it's down it'll be cool to
get that stuff, you know, from here.
It'll probably be It'll probably be
around the same value that it is now.
You know, it'll be a little like a like
a CD. Like a blockchain CD. So, that's
my final verdict. Come check out
mortokens.com. Links to the Telegram are
in the description, by the way. So,
uh let me know what you guys think. Are
you guys still holding pet hex like
idiots or are you Did you give up?
I'm I'm bet I'm going to I'm bet I'm
going to see a good mixture of both in
the comment section. A lot of people
calling everybody retards and a lot of
people saying, "Just wait." I'll talk to
you guys in the next one. Peace.